<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<items>
    <item id="toilet_cleaner">
        <name>Toilet cleaning product</name>
        <description>Cilit BANG, and the dirt is gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="toilet_brush">
        <name>A manky toilet brush</name>
        <description>You find a toilet brush that looks like it's from the roman times. Only Thor himself could scrub hard enough to clean anything with this - It is no more than a stick and sponge that keeps falling off. Ew! The stick end has been sharpened down and has a faded red colour to it... Hmm</description>
    </item>
    <item id="bubble_bath">
        <name>A power scented bubble bath</name>
        <description>You put it in a bath of powerful people.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="rubber_duck">
        <name>A pink rubber duck</name>
        <description>A top essential for every bath. Closely followed by candles.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="kitchen_lunch">
        <name>A Kitchen prepared lunch</name>
        <description>Prepared by the Kremlin's finest cooks this meal consists of a jacket potato, cheese and a bottle of vodka.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="tesco_lunch">
        <name>Tesco meal deal.</name>
        <description>This is Stalin's favourite Meal Deal Combo, Falafel and Houmous Wrap for his main (the mango chutney really compliments the chickpeas) and a Flake for his snack (this delicate milk chocolate bar compliments his choice of main perfectly).</description>
    </item>
    <item id="collar">
        <name>Kirillina's collar</name>
        <description>This huge studded collar initially appears to be better suited a rhino, than a pet. As you look closer you notice the small pink flowers engrained into the fabric of the collar, as well as the name, 'Kirillina'.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="lead">
        <name>Chain lead</name>
        <description>This chain lead looks more in line to haul a ship than a pet.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="list">
        <name>Today's Job list</name>
        <description>1. clean toilet 2. fetch lunch 3. fetch Kirillina 4. run bath 5. dispose of Capitalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="happiness">
        <name>Your Happiness</name>
        <description>It's your first day, your eyes still shine with hope and contentment, this will soon fade.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="bear">
        <name>Tamed bear</name>
        <description>The majestic beast that is Kirillina</description>
    </item>
</items>
